		 <ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsIntro"  >The VIPs
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsOverviewShort"  >
Test your photography skills by taking pictures of both ordinary guests and special VIP guests. Complete all of the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the cat climber.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsOverview"  >
Taking care of animals is your top priority, but as the head of the zoo, you need to attract guests as well. The more guests you have, the more money you raise--and the more money you raise, the better you can take care of your animals!
        <p/>
You've developed a publicity campaign to attract more people to your zoo. Advertisements in newspapers and magazines and on the Internet will promote the idea that all of the guests at your zoo have a fun, unforgettable experience.
        <p/>
You need to take some photographs to use in the advertisements. If you can get the following photos, you'll see an increase in attendance at your zoo:
			<br/>
		*  A guest mimicking an animal. (Hint: Young guests like to mimic cats, moose, flamingos, kangaroos, chimps, and gorillas.)  
			<br/>
		*  A child playing on gorilla climbing bars. (Hint: The gorilla climbing bars become available at 2 stars of zoo fame.)
			<br/>
		*  A guest using binoculars.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:GuestsPhotosGoal"  >
      Take the following photos:
			<br/>
		*  A guest mimicking an animal. (Hint: Young guests like to mimic cats, moose, flamingos, kangaroos, chimps, and gorillas.)  
			<br/>
		*  A child playing on gorilla climbing bars. (Hint: The gorilla climbing bars become available at 2 stars of zoo fame.)
			<br/>
   		*  A guest using binoculars.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:GuestsPhotosGoalDone"  >Congratulations! You have taken photos of guests having fun!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsFame"  >
Your photos worked perfectly with your publicity campaign! New guests are streaming into your zoo.
      <p/>
The zoo's advertising agency advises you that your publicity campaign would be even more successful if you could get some pictures of celebrities or other VIPs visiting your zoo. Obtain a 3-star zoo fame rating to begin attracting VIPs to your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsSpecialGuests"  >
People are talking about your zoo! Now that you've achieved 3-star zoo fame, word of mouth has begun to spread. Rumor has it that two celebrity VIPs are about to visit your zoo: billionaire entrepeneur Billy Siles and world-famous scientist Alvin Einheim.
      <p/>
If you can take photos of these two famous people at your zoo, you'll attract even more guests!
      <p/>
Take the following photos:
      <br/>
		*  Billionaire businessman Billy Siles eating or drinking.
			<br/>
		*  Renowned scientist Alvin Einheim viewing an animal.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsPhotosGoal"  >
      Take the following photos:
			<br/>
		*  Billionaire businessman Billy Siles eating or drinking.
			<br/>
		*  Renowned scientist Alvin Einheim viewing an animal.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPPhotosGoalDone"  >
		Congratulations! You have snapped the required VIP photos!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsDiva"  >
Your photos of famous people in your zoo have attracted a throng of new guests!
      <p/>
Even more exciting news has reached your zoo. Internationally famous diva Dallas Samson is about to visit your zoo. Since she's known to millions for her singing, acting, and ever-changing hairstyle, Dallas Samson's endorsement would raise your zoo to a whole new level of popularity.
      <p/>
Of course, someone as famous as Dallas Samson expects to be entertained during her visit. If you can take a photo of her having a good time dancing near a music rock, she'll endorse your zoo. If not, your zoo will remain terminally uncool.
     <p/>
Take a photo of Dallas Samson dancing near a music rock to win the scenario!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsDivaGoal"  >Take a photo of Dallas Samson dancing near a music rock to win the scenario!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsDivaGoalDone"  >Congratulations! You've managed to snap a photo of Dallas Samson dancing!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsSuccessOverview"  >
Dallas Samson loved her visit to your zoo and will allow you to use your photo as part of your publicity campaign. You've established your park as the "zoo of the stars," and a steady flow of guests is sure to follow. Congratulations on your success!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsBusinessmanEntered"  >
Billionaire Billy Siles has entered the zoo! Take a photo of him eating or drinking.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsScientistEntered"  >
Famous scientist Alvin Einheim has entered your zoo! Take a photo of him viewing an animal.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsDivaEntered"  >
Superstar Dallas Samson has entered your zoo! Take a photo of her dancing near a music rock.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsFailureBusinessman"  >
Businessman Billy Siles left the zoo before you could take a photo of him eating or drinking. Sadly, this spoils your plans for your publicity campaign. Better luck next time!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsFailureScientist"  >
Scientist Alvin Einheimn left the zoo before you could take a photo of him viewing an animal. Unfortunately, this ruins your plans for your publicity campaign. Better luck next time!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsFailureDiva"  >
Superstar Dallas Samson left the zoo before you could take a photo of her dancing near a music rock. You have failed to obtain her endorsement of your publicity campaign. Better luck next time!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsresult"  >Take photos of guests and VIPs!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsOverallGoal"  >Take photos of guests and VIPs to attract more people to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsOverallGoalSuccess"  >Good work! You've gotten world-famous diva Dallas Samson to endorse your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsMimicGoal"  >Take a photo of a guest mimicking an animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsMimicGoalDone"  >You took a photo of a guest mimicking an animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsClimbingBarsGoal"  >Take a photo of a guest using the gorilla climbing bars.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsClimbingBarsGoalDone"  >You took a photo of a guest using the gorilla climbing bars.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsBinocularsGoal"  >Take a photo of a guest using the binoculars.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsBinocularsGoalDone"  >You took a photo of a guest using the binoculars.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsBusinessmanGoal"  >Take a photo of billionaire Billy Siles eating or drinking.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsBusinessmanGoalDone"  >You took a photo of Billy Siles eating or drinking.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsScientistGoal"  >Take a photo of renowned scientist Alvin Einheim viewing an animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsScientistGoalDone"  >You took a photo of Alvin Einheim viewing an animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsFameGoal"  >Achieve a 3-star zoo fame rating.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsFameGoalDone"  >You have achieved a 3-star zoo rating!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsBusinessmanName"  >Billy Siles</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsScientistName"  >Alvin Einheim</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:VIPsDivaName"  >Dallas Samson</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoIntro"  >The Javan Rhinoceros</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoOverviewShort"  >Use your camera to document the mysterious, critically endangered Javan rhino. There's just one catch--you can't get too close! Complete all of the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the cat climber.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoOverview"  >The Javan rhinoceros is one of the most critically endangered animals in the world. Like all rhinos, the Javan rhino has been widely poached for its horn, and experts estimate that there are fewer than 100 of these magnificent creatures left in the wild.
      <p/>
      Conservation of the Javan rhino has been difficult for two reasons. First, zookeepers have had little luck getting Javan rhinos to thrive in zoos, and they have had no luck at all getting them to breed in captivity. Second, scientists know very little about the Javan rhino's behavior. The animal is extremely shy and avoids contact with humans.
      <p/>
      Your zoo has obtained one of these extremely rare animals, and your job is to use your camera to document the Javan rhino's activities. However, rhinos tend to regard any nearby person on the ground as a threat. To avoid stressing the animal, you must take your photos from either a sky tram or an elevated path.
      <p/>
      Take the following photos from an elevated path or a sky tram:
      <br/>
			*  A Javan rhino eating or drinking.
			<br/>
			*  A Javan rhino sleeping.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoPart1Goals"  >
      Take the following photos from an elevated path or a sky tram:
      <br/>
			*  A Javan rhino eating or drinking.
			<br/>
			*  A Javan rhino sleeping.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoPart1GoalsDone"  >You have completed the first set of Javan Rhino photos!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoBehaviors"  >Your photos of the Javan rhino engaging in basic behaviors such as eating and sleeping have been very helpful to the biologists studying the animal. You've been asked to take photos of some of the rhino's more advanced behaviors. Once again, you must take the photos from a sky tram or an elevated path to avoid stressing the animal.
      <p/>
      Take the following photos from an elevated path or a sky tram:
      <br/>
			*  A Javan rhino using a salt lick. (Hint: the salt lick becomes available at 1 star of zoo fame.)
			<br/>
			*  A Javan rhino using a pursuit ball. (Hint: the pursuit ball becomes available at 2 stars of zoo fame.)
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoPart2Goals"  >
      Take the following photos from an elevated path or a sky tram:
      <br/>
			*  A Javan rhino using a salt lick. (Hint: the salt lick becomes available at 1 star of zoo fame.)
			<br/>
			*  A Javan rhino using a pursuit ball. (Hint: the pursuit ball becomes available at 2 stars of zoo fame.)
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoPart2GoalsDone"  >You have completed the second set of Javan Rhino photos!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoFemale"  >
      Good work! Thanks to information obtained from your photos of Javan rhino behaviors, biologists think it may be possible to breed the animal in your zoo. In recognition of your achievement, the zoo's board of directors has given you a $10,000 grant.
      <p/>      
      If you can breed a Javan rhino, it would be a historic breakthrough in the conservation of the species. Your board of directors has obtained a female Javan rhinoceros, which you will find crated at the zoo entrance. The board wants you to accomplish two things with your rhino pair.
		<p/>
First, build your zoo's fame to at least 3-1/2-stars to help publicize the plight of the Javan rhino. When you reach this goal, the board of directors will award you an additional $10,000.
		<p/>
Second, breed your rhinos. To encourage breeding, take good care of the rhinos and make sure their advanced needs are met for an extended period of time. A conservation breeding center (unlocked by winning the Endangered Species campaign) can also help. If you succeed in breeding the pair, then you will be the first zoo ever to breed Javan rhinos in captivity!
      <p/>
After you succeed in breeding the rhinos, take a photo of the baby rhino. As always, you must take the photo from a sky tram or elevated path.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoSuccessOverview"  >
Well done! Not only has your zoo made history by being the first zoo ever to breed the Javan rhino, but your world-famous institution has helped educate the public about the need to protect this critically endangered species.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoOverallGoal"  >Use your camera to document the mysterious Javan rhino.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoEatGoal"  >Take a photo from an elevated path or sky tram of a Javan rhinoceros eating or drinking.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoEatGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a Javan rhino eating or drinking!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoSleepGoal"  >Take a photo from an elevated path or sky tram of a Javan rhinoceros sleeping.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoSleepGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a Javan rhino sleeping!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoSaltLickGoal"  >Take a photo from an elevated path or a sky tram of a Javan rhino using a salt lick.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoSaltLickGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a Javan rhino using a salt lick!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoPursuitBallGoal"  >Take a photo from an elevated path or a sky tram of a Javan rhino using a pursuit ball.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoPursuitBallGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a Javan rhino using a pursuit ball!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoBabyGoal"  >Take a photo from an elevated path or a sky tram of a baby Javan rhinoceros.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoBabyGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a baby Javan rhino from an elevated path or sky tram!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoFameGoal"  >Achieve 3-1/2 stars of zoo fame to obtain a $10,000 grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:JavanRhinoFameGoalDone"  >Your zoo has reached 3-1/2 stars of fame!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryIntro"  >The Cat Sanctuary</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryOverviewShort"  >Transform a small sanctuary for big cats into a successful zoo--and practice your photography skills along the way! Complete this scenario to unlock the cat climber.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryOverview"  >A local charity has run a private cat sanctuary for the last few years. The cat sanctuary cares for a handful of exotic big cats that were originally bought as pets while cubs but then abandoned by their owners when the cats became too large and unmanageable.
      <p/>
      The charity's board of directors can no longer afford to run the cat sanctuary without additional outside funds. To keep the sanctuary open, the board has decided to transform the cat sanctuary into a full-fledged zoo that charges admission and showcases a variety of animals.
      <p/>
      Before you can open the zoo to the public, however, you need to obtain the appropriate permits from the local authorities. They want photographic evidence that the cats in the sanctuary are cared for properly. Until you provide them with this evidence, you cannot open the zoo.
      <p/>
      Take the following photographs:
      <br/>
			*  A photo of a happy, healthy jaguar.
		<br/>
			*  A photo of a happy, healthy cheetah.
		<br/>
			*  A photo of a happy, healthy lion.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:HealthyAnimalsGoal"  >
      Take the following photographs:
      <br/>
			*  A photo of a happy, healthy jaguar.
		<br/>
			*  A photo of a happy, healthy cheetah.
		<br/>
			*  A photo of a happy, healthy lion.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:HealthyAnimalsGoalDone"  >
      You have taken pictures of a healthy jaguar, cheetah, and lion!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryGuests"  >Your photos convinced the local authorities that you take proper care of your animals. They have issued the required permits so you may now open your zoo.
      <br/> 
      Your zoo's board of directors has even more good news. Local philanthropist J.D. McPherson has donated $2,000 to your new zoo! Better yet he has promised to give an additional $15,000 if you can convince him that your zoo will be a success. Once your zoo has been visited by 75 guests, Mr. McPherson will donate $15,000 to your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryLynx"  >More than 75 people have visited your zoo! As promised, you've received $15,000 from local philanthropist J.D. McPherson. The money will come in handy while expanding the zoo.
      <p/>
      To remain true to the zoo's original roots as a cat sanctuary, the board of directors would like you to obtain a critically endangered Spanish lynx for your zoo. If you can obtain this rare animal, zoo benefactor J.D. McPherson will give the zoo a $40,000 grant. Mr. McPherson has just one request: that you take a photo of the lynx that he can display in his office.
      <p/>
      Take a photo of a Spanish lynx using a beef shank to receive a $40,000 grant.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryPanther"  >
      Zoo benefactor J.D. McPherson is delighted with both the lynx and the photo you took for him. He's awarded your zoo a $40,000 grant.
      <p/>
      Mr. McPherson wants your zoo to become the premiere zoo for big cats in your area. To achieve that, he wants you to help preserve the critically endangered Florida panther by obtaining one for your zoo. As with the lynx, Mr. McPherson would like a photo of the animal as a souvenir.
      <p/>
      To complete this scenario, take a photo of a happy, healthy Florida panther resting on a large wetlands rock.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuarySuccessOverview"  >
      By obtaining a rare Florida panther, you've established your zoo as the leading big cat conservation facility in the region. You've also made quite an impression on J.D. McPherson, who has pledged to support your zoo in the future. Good work!
      <p/>
      You have unlocked the cat climber! The cat climber will be available in all of your future Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species games.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryOverallGoal"  >Transform a small cat sanctuary into a successful zoo. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryJaguarGoal"  >Take a photo of a happy, healthy jaguar. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryJaguarGoalDone"  >You took a photo of a happy, healthy jaguar. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryCheetahGoal"  >Take a photo of a happy, healthy cheetah. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryCheetahGoalDone"  >You took a photo of a happy, healthy cheetah. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryLionGoal"  >Take a photo of a happy, healthy lion. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryLionGoalDone"  >You took a photo of a happy, healthy lion. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryGuestsGoal"  >Get 75 guests to visit your zoo. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryGuestsGoalDone"  >More than 75 guests have visited your zoo. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryLynxGoal"  >Take a photo of a happy, healthy Spanish lynx eating from a beef shank. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryLynxGoalDone"  >You took a photo of a happy, healthy Spanish lynx eating from a beef shank. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryPantherGoal"  >Take a photo of a happy, healthy Florida panther resting on a large wetlands rock. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafari:CatSanctuaryPantherGoalDone"  >You took a photo of a happy, healthy Florida panther resting on a large wetlands rock. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafariLabels:PhotoSafariCampaignshort"  >Photo Safari</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafariLabels:PhotoSafariCampaignS1"  >The VIPs</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafariLabels:PhotoSafariCampaignS1short"  >The VIPs</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafariLabels:PhotoSafariCampaignS2"  >The Javan Rhinoceros</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafariLabels:PhotoSafariCampaignS2short"  >The Javan Rhino</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafariLabels:PhotoSafariCampaignS3"  >The Cat Sanctuary</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoSafariLabels:PhotoSafariCampaignS3short"  >The Cat Sanctuary</LOC_STRING>
   
</ZT2Strings>
