<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_conservationarea:entry"  >Conservation Areas</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_conservationarea:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
Conservation areas in Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species are enclosed by <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_conservationfences:entry"><u><color r="255" g="231" b="135">conservation fences.</color></u></a> To help protect their fragile environments, conservation areas are off-limits to most types of development. You cannot use the biome brush, alter the terrain, recycle plants and rocks, or place most buildings and scenery within conservation areas.                  
                  <p/>
However, you may build elevated paths and place sky tram poles inside conservation areas. You may also place animals, animal food, and enrichment items inside conservation areas, as long as it does not flatten the terrain. A conservation area can be an effective natural exhibit for endangered species suited to the biome.                              
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_rewardobjects:entry"  >Reward Objects</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_rewardobjects:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
You earn reward objects by winning <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_awards:entry"><u><color r="255" g="231" b="135">awards,</color></u></a> playing <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_challenge:entry"><u><color r="255" g="231" b="135">challenges,</color></u></a>challenges, or completing <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_campaign:entry"><u><color r="255" g="231" b="135">campaigns.</color></u></a> Some reward objects are available only in the game in which you won them. "Unlocked" reward objects are available in every game of Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species you play after they're unlocked.
<p/>
Here are the reward objects in Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species and how you get them.
<p/>
Balloon bouquet: Have an endangered species baby.
<br/>Blimp: Win the 20th Anniversary Award.
<br/>Enhanced zoo gate: Win the Zoo Tycoon Award.
<br/>Enhanced zoo wall columns: Win the Endangered Species Award.
<br/>Enhanced zoo walls: Win the Endangered Animal Release Effort Award.
<br/>Baby Animals Statue: Win the Endangered Babies Award.
<br/>Face painting kiosk: Win the Entertainment Donation Achievement Award.
<br/>Headset kiosk: Win the Educational Donation Achievement Award.
<br/>Photo kiosk: Win the Endangered Species Photographer Award.
<br/>Sky tower: Win the Tour Rating Achievement Award.
<br/>Upgraded Jeep&#xAE; vehicles: Win a Tour Tycoon Award.
<br/>Upgraded sky tram vehicles: Win a Transportation Tycoon Award.
<br/>Zoo attendance statue: Win the Zoo Attendance 20,000 Guests Award.
<p/>
Endangered species theme: Unlock by completing any two endangered species challenges in challenge mode.
<br/>Jungle theme: Unlock by completing any five photo challenges in challenge mode.
<br/>Safari theme: Unlock by completing any five game challenges in challenge mode.
<p/>
Cat climber: Unlock by completing the Photo Safari campaign. 
<br/>Conservation breeding center: Unlock by completing the Endangered Species campaign.
<br/>Decorated vehicle gate: Unlock by completing the Transportation campaign. 
<p/>
Flower arch: Unlock by completing the Troubled Zoos campaign.
<br/>Flower post: Unlock by completing the Zookeeper In Training campaign.
<br/>Gilded statue: Unlock by completing the Mysterious Panda campaign.
<br/>Globe statue: Unlock by completing the Globe campaign.
<br/>Sundial: Unlock by completing the Prevent Animal Abuse campaign.           
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_layingdownroads:entry"  >Laying Down Roads</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_layingdownroads:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
To use Jeep&#xAE; vehicles, you need one or more Jeep vehicle stations connected to a completed road circuit. Once a circuit is complete, the Jeep station will open and you can buy vehicles for it. Place paths leading to your Jeep vehicle station entrances so that your guests can enter and exit.
<p/>
Note that all roads in Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species are one-way (you can reverse the direction at a Jeep vehicle station.) To make a valid circuit, avoid dead ends and breaks in the road.
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_layingdownskytramcable:entry"  >Laying Down Sky Tram Cable</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_layingdownskytramcable:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
To use sky trams, you need one or more sky tram stations connected to a closed circuit of sky tram cable. Once a circuit is complete, the sky tram station will open and you can buy vehicles for it. Place paths leading to your sky tram station entrances so that your guests can enter and exit.
      <p/>
Sky tram poles are used to place sky tram cable. To connect cable from a pole to a sky tram station, select the sky tram pole from the transporation buy panel, click the desired location to build the pole, and then click the station to connect the cable from the pole to the station. To adjust the height of a sky tram pole, place the cursor over the tip of a sky tram pole so that the hand cursor appears, then click and hold. Now pull up and down to adjust the pole to the desired height.
      <p/>
To create a two-station circuit in the minimum amount of space, connect the first station to the second station, then run a cable directly back from the second station to the first station. The vehicles will turn around inside the station building.                            
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_creatingelevatedpaths:entry"  >Creating Elevated Paths</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_creatingelevatedpaths:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
There are two basic steps to create an elevated path. First, build a ramp that connects your elevated path to the terrain. Then, build a flat elevated path where you want it to go. From there you can add additional paths and ramps, including ramps down. If you're having trouble getting a down ramp to connect to the terrain, try flattening the terrain first. If you're still having trouble, lower the terrain a bit, flatten it, then try connecting the ramp again.
     <p/>
Buildings and other objects may be placed on top of flat elevated paths. You can even build entire food courts, playgrounds, and sky tram stations on elevated platforms! Elevated paths can also be built over conservation areas, making them the perfect way to get your guests over these protected regions.
      <p/>
Path supports are automatically placed when you build elevated paths. You may delete the path supports if you like.                            
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tours:entry"  >Tours</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tours:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
Guests love an exciting tour while riding in Jeep&#xAE; vehicles and sky trams. The more your guests enjoy a tour, the higher their tour rating for the transportation circuit--and the higher the tour rating, the more you receive in tour donations!
     <p/>
While they are touring guests like to see animals, animal shelters, biome-appropriate foliage and rocks, themed buildings, fountains, arches, flowerbeds, and tour objects. Tour objects an especially good way to grab the attention of your touring guests!
     <p/>
Guests like variety in their tours, and may get bored of seeing too much of the same thing during a single tour.                           
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>  
   
</ZT2Strings>
