<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:welcome"  >Welcome! In this tutorial you'll learn about elevated paths, endangered species, and conservation areas. When you're ready to begin, click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openQuickStatsHeading"  >Quick Stats Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openQuickStats"  >As you might expect, endangered species are the stars of Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species. To find out which species are endangered, click the Zoo Quick Stats button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openQuickStatsCompleted"  >Good! The Quick Stats panel is a great way to check up on the animals in your zoo. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectPandaBearHeading"  >Select Red Panda</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectPandaBear"  >Click one of the red pandas in the list to see its conservation status.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectPandaBearCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:closeQuickStatsHeading"  >Close Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:closeQuickStats"  >Good! Before closing the Quick Stats panel, notice that you can move it around on the screen so you can keep it open while doing other things, such as moving animals. Now click the X button to close the Quick Stats panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:closeQuickStatsCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewAnimalGeneralInfoHeading"  >General Information Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewAnimalGeneralInfo"  >Click the General Information tab for the red panda.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewAnimalGeneralInfoCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewEndangermentInfoTextHeading"  >Conservation Status</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewEndangermentInfoText"  >N/A</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewEndangermentInfoTextCompleted"  >The General Information panel displays an animal's conservation status: Lower Risk, Vulnerable, Endangered, or Critically Endangered. The red panda is endangered, which means that it is at high risk of extinction in the wild unless it is protected. Zoos can play an important role in conserving endangered species. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewBreedingCenterInfoTextHeading"  >Conservation Breeding Center</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewBreedingCenterInfoText"  >N/A</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewBreedingCenterInfoTextCompleted"  >Endangered and critically endangered species are more sensitive to their environments and harder to breed. The conservation breeding center makes it easier to breed these species. You can unlock this building by completing the Endangered Species campaign. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewConservationAreaHeading"  >Conservation Areas</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewConservationArea"  >Conservation areas are special regions protected by conservation fence. Scroll to the conservation area in the middle of the map. When you find it, Conservation Area appears on the screen.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewConservationAreaCompleted"  >Good! To protect the delicate environment within a conservation area, you cannot change the landscape or build fences, paths, buildings, or scenery. However, you can place animal food, enrichment items, sky tram poles, and elevated paths. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewElevatedPathIntroductionHeading"  >Elevated Paths</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewElevatedPathIntroduction"  >N/A</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:viewElevatedPathIntroductionCompleted"  >Elevated paths give your guests a better view of animals and are a great way to bridge obstacles such as rivers, chasms, or conservation areas. Ready to learn how to build an elevated path? Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openConstructionPanelHeading"  >Construction Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openConstructionPanel"  >To build an elevated path, click the Construction button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openConstructionPanelCompleted"  >Great! Notice the new Elevated Paths tab. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openElevatedPathPanelHeading"  >Elevated Paths Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openElevatedPathPanel"  >Click the Elevated Paths tab.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openElevatedPathPanelCompleted"  >The three buttons in the upper left let you build a level elevated path, a ramp up, or a ramp down. The two buttons in the upper right let you increase or decrease the height of unplaced level elevated paths. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectRampUpToolHeading"  >Ramp Up Button</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectRampUpTool"  >Click the Ramp Up button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectRampUpToolCompleted"  >Good! Next, you'll place the ramp in just the right spot to connect it to the existing elevated path. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRampUpElevatedPathHeading"  >Build Ramp Up</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRampUpElevatedPath"  >With the Ramp Up button selected, position the cursor in the empty space between the hotdog and hamburger stands. Click to place the starting point of the ramp, then drag the cursor to the empty space between the two giant sequoia trees. When the ramp appears where you want it, click again to build it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRampUpElevatedPathCompleted"  >Great! Next, you'll learn to connect a level elevated path to the ramp. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectFlatElevatedPathToolHeading"  >Level Elevated Path Button</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectFlatElevatedPathTool"  >Click the Level Elevated Path button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectFlatElevatedPathToolCompleted"  >Building a level elevated path is similar to building a ramp. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeFlatElevatedPathHeading"  >Build a Level Elevated Path</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeFlatElevatedPath"  >With the Level Elevated Path button selected, place the cursor over the ramp you just built. When the cursor turns green, click to anchor the path to the ramp, and then drag the cursor toward the path you're connecting to. When the path appears where you want it, click again to build it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeFlatElevatedPathCompleted"  >Good! You can use elevated paths to connect existing elevated paths or to build viewing platforms over exhibits. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRailingReplacement1Heading"  >Replacing Railing</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRailingReplacement1"  >To change the railing on your elevated paths, click the elevated path wood railing.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRailingReplacement1Completed"  >Replacing railing is similar to replacing fences. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRailingReplacement2Heading"  >Replace Wood Railing</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRailingReplacement2"  >Click the existing railing, drag the cursor over the section you want to replace, and then click again.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRailingReplacement2Completed"  >Good! Next you'll learn to place objects on an elevated path. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openSceneryPanelHeading"  >Scenery Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openSceneryPanel"  >Click the Scenery Items tab.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openSceneryPanelCompleted"  >Boy, there are a lot of scenery items! Next, you'll learn to filter them to find what you're looking for. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openObjectFiltersPanelHeading"  >Construction Filter</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openObjectFiltersPanel"  >Click the Construction Filter button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openObjectFiltersPanelCompleted"  >Finding items is quick and easy if you filter them by type, product, or theme. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectStatueFilterHeading"  >Statues Filter</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectStatueFilter"  >Scroll the list until you find Statues, and then click it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectStatueFilterCompleted"  >Now only statues appear in the list. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRhinoStatueHeading"  >Rhino Statue</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRhinoStatue"  >Click the rhino statue, and then place it on your elevated path.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:placeRhinoStatueCompleted"  >Good! You can place nearly anything on elevated paths, except landscaping items such as plants. You can also place items under elevated paths if there's enough space. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openViewFiltersPanelHeading"  >Object Filter Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openViewFiltersPanel"  >To learn about more great new features, click the Object Filter button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:openViewFiltersPanelCompleted"  >The Object Filter lets you show or hide plants and buildings. It also has two new features. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectGuestViewFilterHeading"  >Guest View Area</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectGuestViewFilter"  >Click the Guest View Area button to see which parts of an exhibit a guest can see.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectGuestViewFilterCompleted"  >When Guest View Area is on, an eye cursor appears that shows you what guests can see from a location. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:DisplayGuestViewHeading"  >Eye Cursor</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:DisplayGuestView"  >To try it out, move the eye cursor to the elevated path facing the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:DisplayGuestViewCompleted"  >The highlighted area shows what a guest can see from that location. Guest View Area is a great tool for building the perfect exhibit. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectGuestViewFilterOffHeading"  >Turn Off Filter</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectGuestViewFilterOff"  >Click the button to turn off the Guest View Area filter.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectGuestViewFilterOffCompleted"  >The other new feature on the Object Filter panel lets you see what is under your elevated paths. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectElevatedPathFilterHeading"  >Elevated Path Slider</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectElevatedPathFilter"  >To make your elevated paths transparent, click the slider and drag it all the way down.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:selectElevatedPathFilterCompleted"  >Notice that the elevated path is transparent. If you want to make it visible again, just drag the slider back up. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial1:tutorial_complete"  >
         
         Congratulations! You've finished the elevated paths tutorial. 
      
         
         <p/>
         
         
      To play the next tutorial and learn about sky trams, click the check button. 
      
         
         <p/>
         
         
      To return to the Main Menu, click the X button.
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:welcome"  >Welcome! In this tutorial you'll learn how to create sky tram tours and place tour objects. When you're ready to begin, click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:viewSkytramInfoTextHeading"  >Sky Trams</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:viewSkytramInfoText"  >N/A</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:viewSkytramInfoTextCompleted"  >Sky trams provide guests or yourself an exciting, bird's-eye tour of your zoo. Ready to learn to build a sky tram? Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openconstructionheading"  >Construction Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openconstruction"  >Click the Construction button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openconstructioncompleted"  >Notice the Transportation tab. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openTransportationPanelHeading"  >Transportation Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openTransportationPanel"  >Click the Transportation tab.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openTransportationPanelCompleted"  >The Transportation tab includes everything you need to build a sky tram circuit. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeSkyStationHeading"  >Sky Tram Station</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeSkyStation"  >A sky tram circuit needs at least one sky tram station. Click the sky tram station, and then position it between the four flower beds on the map. Use the > key to rotate the entrance toward the path so guests can enter, and then click to place the station.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeSkyStationCompleted"  >Good job! The sky tram station lets guests board and exit your sky tram tour. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:connectSkyPoleToSkyStationHeading"  >Connect Sky Tram Cable</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:connectSkyPoleToSkyStation"  >To connect cable to your sky tram station, click the sky tram pole, and then click the sky tram station.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:connectSkyPoleToSkyStationCompleted"  >Great! You have connected a cable to your sky tram station. Now you need to place poles around the zoo. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeSkyPoleHeading"  >Connect Sky Tram Pole</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeSkyPole"  >Click the pole cursor on the next accessible snow spot, moving counter-clockwise around the zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeSkyPoleCompleted"  >Good! Now place another pole on the next spot of snow.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:closeSkyPoleCircuitHeading"  >Complete Circuit</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:closeSkyPoleCircuit"  >Terrific! Now place a sky tram pole on each of the other snow spots in the zoo. After you place the last pole, click the sky tram station to connect the cable and complete the circuit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:closeSkyPoleCircuitCompleted"  >Congratulations! You have completed a sky tram circuit. Your station has opened for business and you can now buy sky tram carts for your guests to ride. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:selectSkyStationHeading"  >Select Sky Tram Station</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:selectSkyStation"  >To buy sky tram carts, click the sky tram station. You may need to right-click to clear the pole icon from your cursor first.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:selectSkyStationCompleted"  >Note that the station opened when the circuit was completed. If you break the circuit by removing poles, the station will close. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:select1SeaterHeading"  >One-Seat Cart</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:select1Seater"  >To buy a cart for your sky tram tour, click the one-seat cart.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:select1SeaterCompleted"  >Good! The one-seat cart transports one guest. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:buy1SeaterHeading"  >Buy Two One-Seat Carts</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:buy1Seater"  >You want to buy two one-seat sky tram carts, so click the Buy Selected Vehicle button two times.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:buy1SeaterCompleted"  >After you buy a cart, it appears at the station and then moves along the tour route. Guests will come to take your tour and ride in the carts. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openSkyStationInfoHeading"  >Building Status</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openSkyStationInfo"  >To see how many guests are riding your sky tram, click the Building Status button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openSkyStationInfoCompleted"  >The Building Status panel shows how many carts you have, how many guests are riding, and the sky tram's tour rating. Guests especially enjoy seeing animals, trees, statues, and themed buildings from a sky tram. The more guests see, the higher your tour rating and tour donations.  Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:viewTourRatingInfoTextHeading"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:viewTourRatingInfoText"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:viewTourRatingInfoTextCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openDonationStationInfoHeading"  >Donations</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openDonationStationInfo"  >Some guests give a tour donation after riding a sky tram. The higher your tour rating, the more money you'll make in tour donations. To see how much you've earned in tour donations, click the View Donations button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openDonationStationInfoCompleted"  >Hmmm, guests haven't donated much yet! Maybe you need to add some tour objects to make your tour more exciting. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openSceneryPanelTourHeading"  >Scenery Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openSceneryPanelTour"  >You can place tour objects to improve your tour rating and donations. To place tour objects, click the Scenery Items tab.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openSceneryPanelTourCompleted"  >There are a lot of exciting tour objects to dazzle your guests while they are riding in a sky tram or ground vehicle.  Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openObjectFiltersPanel_TourHeading"  >Object Filter</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openObjectFiltersPanel_Tour"  >To sort tour objects, click the Object filter.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:openObjectFiltersPanel_TourCompleted"  >The Object filter lets you to find objects quickly and easily! Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:selectObjectFilter_TourHeading"  >Tour Object Filter</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:selectObjectFilter_Tour"  >Scroll the list until you find Tour Objects, and then click it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:selectObjectFilter_TourCompleted"  >Now only tour objects are displayed. The higher your zoo fame, the more tour objects you can choose from. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeBatCaveHeading"  >Bat Cave</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeBatCave"  >Click the bat cave, and then place it near your sky tram route.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:placeBatCaveCompleted"  >Good work! The bat cave is full of squeaking, fluttering bats that your guests will enjoy seeing from the sky tram! Click the check button to complete the tutorial.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial2:tutorial_complete"  >
         
         Congratulations! You've finished the sky tram tutorial! 
      
         
         <p/>
         
         
To play the next tutorial and learn how to create Jeep&#xAE; vehicle tours, click the check button. 
      
         
         <p/>
         
         
      To return to the Main Menu, click the X button.
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:welcome"  >Welcome! In this tutorial you'll learn how to place Jeep&#xAE; vehicle stations and roads and how to ride ground vehicles in first-person mode. When you're ready to begin, click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:openConstructionHeading"  >Construction Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:openConstruction"  >This zoo has a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle circuit that's almost fully built. You just need to add a few touches to finish it. Ready to learn how? First, click the Construction button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:openConstructionCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectTransportationTabHeading"  >Transportation Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectTransportationTab"  >Click the Transportation tab.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectTransportationTabCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundStationBuyButtonHeading"  >Jeep&#xAE; Vehicle Station</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundStationBuyButton"  >A Jeep&#xAE; vehicle tour needs at least one station. Click the Jeep&#xAE; vehicle station.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundStationBuyButtonCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:placeGroundStationHeading"  >Place Jeep&#xAE; Vehicle Station</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:placeGroundStation"  >Position the Jeep&#xAE; vehicle station between the four flower beds. Use the > key to rotate the building entrance toward the path so guests can enter, and then click to place the building.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:placeGroundStationCompleted"  >Great! Next, you'll learn to place road. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundTrackBuyButtonHeading"  >Road</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundTrackBuyButton"  >Click the road so you can place it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundTrackBuyButtonCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:connectGroundCircuitHeading"  >Complete Road Circuit</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:connectGroundCircuit"  >Click the empty space between the two flowerbeds beside the Jeep&#xAE; vehicle station, drag the cursor toward the road in the camel exhibit, and then click to connect the roads and complete the circuit. Don't worry about the fence that's in the way.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:connectGroundCircuitCompleted"  >Excellent! You've completed the road circuit. Notice that a vehicle gate was automatically built in the fence. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundStationHeading"  >Select Station</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundStation"  >Now that you've completed the road circuit, your Jeep&#xAE; vehicle station is open for business. Click the station so you can buy Jeep vehicles and guests can ride your tour. You may need to right-click to clear the road icon from your cursor.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectGroundStationCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:purchaseVehiclesHeading"  >Buy Jeep&#xAE; Vehicles</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:purchaseVehicles"  >You want to buy five Jeep&#xAE; vehicles, so click the Buy Selected Vehicle button five times.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:purchaseVehiclesCompleted"  >When you buy a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle it appears at the Jeep vehicle station and then moves along the tour route. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:openConstruction2Heading"  >Construction Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:openConstruction2"  >Notice that the road crosses a pedestrian path. Jeep&#xAE; vehicles automatically slow to let pedestrians pass, which can lead to traffic jams. To place a crossing gate, click the Construction button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:openConstruction2Completed"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectTransportationTab2Heading"  >Transportation</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectTransportationTab2"  >Click the Transportation tab.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectTransportationTab2Completed"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectCrossingGateBuyButtonHeading"  >Select Crossing Gate</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectCrossingGateBuyButton"  >Click the crossing gate. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:selectCrossingGateBuyButtonCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:placeCrossingGateHeading"  >Place Crossing Gate</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:placeCrossingGate"  >Now place the crossing gate where the road crosses the pedestrian path.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:placeCrossingGateCompleted"  >Good work! The crossing gate automatically lowers when a vehicle approaches, so traffic will now flow more smoothly at the intersection. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:enterFirstPersonHeading"  >Riding Vehicle</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:enterFirstPerson"  >You can ride in both sky trams and Jeep&#xAE; vehicles. To ride in a Jeep vehicle, click the button to enter Zoo Guest mode.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:enterFirstPersonCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:boardVehicleHeading"  >Board Jeep&#xAE; Vehicle</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:boardVehicle"  >Now that you're in first-person mode, walk up beside a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle and then press Spacebar to board it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:boardVehicleCompleted"  >Great! Take a moment to sit back and enjoy the ride! When you're ready to continue, click the check button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:changeSeatPositionHeading"  >Change Seat Position</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:changeSeatPosition"  >To change seats while riding inside a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle, press a seat number (for example, press 2 to sit in the passenger seat).</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:changeSeatPositionCompleted"  >In the Jeep&#xAE; Wrangler you can sit in seats 1 through 4, while in the Jeep Commander you can sit in seats 1 through 7. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:photoModeHeading"  >Camera Mode</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:photoMode"  >To take photos of the passing scenery while riding inside a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle, click the Photo Safari View button (or press C) to enter camera mode.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:photoModeCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:takePictureHeading"  >Take Photo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:takePicture"  >Now press the Spacebar to take a photo!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:takePictureCompleted"  >Great shot! You can also take photos while riding in sky trams. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:overheadViewHeading"  >Overhead Mode</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:overheadView"  >Click the Overhead View button to restore your view.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:overheadViewCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:zoostatsHeading"  >Zoo Stats</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:zoostats"  >Now, let's see what kind of rewards your zoo is reaping. Click the Zoo Stats button or the zoo's front gate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:zoostatsCompleted"  >null</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:awardsHeading"  >Awards Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:awards"  >Click the Awards tab.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:awardsCompleted"  >The Awards panel shows awards you've won, awards you can earn in the future, prerequisites, and your progress toward winning awards that require multiple things, such as 100 zoo visitors. Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:persistantAwardsHeading"  >Persistent Awards</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:persistantAwards"  >The Awards panel also shows reward objects that you can earn. Some reward objects can be only be used in your current game. But persistent awards, unlock reward items that you can use in every game that you play! Click the Persistent Awards button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:persistantAwardsCompleted"  >Try to collect all of the different awards and reward objects to become the ultimate zoo tycoon! Click the check button to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="xp1_tutorial3:tutorial_complete"  >
         Congratulations! You have completed the tutorials for Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species. Now you're ready to use everything you've learned to explore the game. In addition to the new features discussed in the tutorials, there are also 20 new animals, 20 new challenges, 3 new campaigns, and dozens of new objects to enjoy. Good luck! 
			<p/>
			If you'd like to learn more about how to play Zoo Tycoon 2, try the other tutorials. Tutorials are marked with the book icon.
<img src="ui/shared/tutorial_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>			
         <p/>
         
      Press the X button to return to the Main Menu.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_campaignname"  >Endangered Species Tutorials</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T1"  >Tutorial 1: Elevated Paths</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T1short"  >Elevated Paths</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T1overviewshort"  >Learn about elevated paths, endangered species, and conservation areas in your zoo!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T2"  >Tutorial 2: Sky Trams</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T2short"  >Sky Trams</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T2overviewshort"  >Learn how to create sky tram tours and place tour objects!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T3"  >Tutorial 3: Jeep&#xAE; Vehicles</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T3short"  >Jeep&#xAE; Vehicles</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:xp1_T3overviewshort"  >Learn how to place Jeep&#xAE; vehicle stations and roads and how to ride Jeep vehicles in first-person mode!</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
