<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHGenericPhotoPhotos"  >Zoo News Monthly</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHGenericPhoto"  >          
			Zoo News Monthly wants to feature an article on your zoo, and they need photos for the story. After you provide the photos and they run the article, there will be a positive impact on attendance at your zoo for the next three months while the magazine is displayed on newsstands. They would like photos of:     
			<br/>         
		*  A jaguar swimming in the water.   
			<br/>     
		*  An ibex resting in a stable. 
			<br/>
		*  A moose rubbing its antlers on a tree. 
			<br/>
   			Difficulty: Moderate
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHGenericPhotoShort"  >  
   			Take the following photos:  
			<p/>   
		*  A jaguar swimming in the water.    
			<br/> 
		*  An ibex resting in a stable. 
			<br/> 
		*  A moose rubbing its antlers on a tree.
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHGenericPhotoSuccess"  >The Zoo News article looks fantastic, and the photos were so impressive that your zoo has been mentioned on the magazine cover! Your attendance is sure to get a boost while the magazine is on newsstands.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHGenericPhotoSuccessShort"  >Your photos were fantastic. Your zoo was mentioned on the cover of Zoo News Monthly!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_GenericPicture1"  >Take a photo of a jaguar swimming in the water.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_GenericPicture2"  >Take a photo of an ibex resting in a stable.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_GenericPicture3"  >Take a photo of a moose rubbing its antlers.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHInternationalGeographerPhotos"  >Global Cartographer</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHInternationalGeographer"  >
Global Cartographer magazine is looking for photos of animals that can survive in extreme environments. If you can provide a photo of a caribou in the tundra biome and a photo of a dromedary camel in the desert biome, the magazine will pay you $2,000.  
			<br/>
   			Difficulty: Easy
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHInternationalGeographerShort"  >  
	   		Take the following photos:  
			<br/>   
		*  A caribou in the tundra biome.    
			<br/> 
		*  A dromedrary camel in the desert biome.
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHInternationalGeographerSuccess"  >Your photos of the caribou and the dromedary camel were a big hit with Global Cartographer magazine. The magazine has paid you $2,000 for the photos.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHInternationalGeographerSuccessShort"  >Global Cartographer magazine was very happy with your photos and has paid you $2,000.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_CaribouInTundra"  >Take a photo of a caribou in the tundra biome.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_DromedaryCamelInDesert"  >Take a photo of a dromedrary camel in the desert biome.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHADayInTheLifePhotos"  >A Day at the Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHADayInTheLife"  >A prominent magazine would like to publish a photo essay on "A Day at the Zoo." They are willing to pay $1,000 for photos of ordinary day-to-day activities in your zoo. Specifically, they would like photos of:
			<br/>*  Guests entering through your zoo gate.
			<br/>*  A maintenance worker emptying a trash can.
			<br/>*  A zookeeper filling a food dish.
			<p/>
   			Difficulty: Easy
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHADayInTheLifeShort"  >Take the following photos:  
			<br/>*  Guests entering through your zoo gate.    
			<br/>*  A maintenance worker emptying a trash can. 
			<br/>*  A zookeeper filling a food dish.
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHADayInTheLifeSuccess"  >The magazine has paid you $1,000 for the photos. Their article, "A Day at %s," was very successful, and your zoo has become slightly more famous as a result!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHADayInTheLifeSuccessShort"  >The magazine has paid you $1,000 for the photos, and the article has made your zoo more famous!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_GuestsAndZooGate"  >Take a photo of a guest by the zoo gate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EmptyingGarbage"  >Take a photo of a maintenance worker emptying the trash.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_FillingFoodDish"  >Take a photo of a zookeeper filling a food dish.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHPosterCampaignPhotos"  >Promotional Poster Campaign</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHPosterCampaign"  >          
Your public relations department has a plan to brighten up your zoo and attract more business. The public relations experts feel that a series of promotional posters showing zoo guests enjoying themselves will draw more people to your zoo and also bring a smile to visitors already in the park. They want you to take three different photos for the posters:       
			<br/>         
		*  A guest dancing next to a sound rock.   
			<br/>     
		*  A guest talking to a hand puppet gift item. 
			<br/>
		*  A guest mimicking one of the animals. 
			<br/>
   			Difficulty: Moderate
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHPosterCampaignShort"  >  
	   		Take the following photos:  
			<br/>   
		*  A guest dancing next to a sound rock.    
			<br/> 
		*  A guest talking to a hand puppet gift item. 
			<br/> 
		*  A guest mimicking one of the animals.
   			<p/>
Hint: Young guests like to mimic cats, moose, flamingos, kangaroos, chimps, and gorillas.
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHPosterCampaignSuccess"  >Your publicity photos were a big hit! The posters have attracted more guests to your zoo, and putting up the posters in your zoo has made all of your guests a little happier.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHPosterCampaignSuccessShort"  >Your poster photos were fantastic! Most guests are visiting the zoo, and all guests in the zoo are a little happier.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_GuestDance"  >Take a photo of a guest dancing next to a sound rock.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_GuestTalkPuppet"  >Take a photo of a guest talking to a hand puppet gift item.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_GuestMimic"  >Take a photo of a young guest mimicking an animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHZooArchitecturePhotos"  >Zoo Architecture Magazine</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHZooArchitecture"  >Zoo Architecture Magazine is preparing a photo essay on how pedestrians use zoos. If you can provide them with a photo of at least four guests on an elevated path, the magazine will pay you $1,500.    
			<br/>
   			Difficulty: Easy</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHZooArchitectureShort"  >Take a photo of at least four guests on an elevated path to earn $1,500.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHZooArchitectureSuccess"  >Zoo Architecture Magazine raved about your elevated path photo! The magazine has paid you $1,500 for the photo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHZooArchitectureSuccessShort"  >Your photo of four guests on an elevated path earned you $1,500.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_ElevatedPathWithGuests"  >Take a photo of at least four guests on an elevated path.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHLeisureTransportationPhotos"  >Leisure Transportation Federation</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHLeisureTransportation"  >Consultants from the Leisure Transportation Federation have advised you that building a zoo tour using Jeep&#xAE; vehicles will make your zoo more popular. If you can take certain photos, the federation will put together a publicity campaign that will attract more guests to your zoo. Here are the photos you need to take:
			<br/>
		*  A photo of three or more guests riding in a Jeep vehicle.   
			<br/>     
		*  While riding in a Jeep vehicle, take a photo of one animal species.
		<br/>
		*  While riding in a Jeep vehicle, take a photo of a second animal species.
		<p/>   
			Difficulty: Moderate		
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHLeisureTransportationShort"  >Take the following photos:
			<br/>
		*  A photo of three or more guests riding in a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle.   
			<br/>     
		*  While riding in a Jeep vehicle, take a photo of one animal species.
		<br/>
		*  While riding in a Jeep vehicle, take a photo of a second animal species.
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHLeisureTransportationSuccess"  >The promotional campaign featuring photos taken from Jeep&#xAE; vehicles was a big success! The publicity has attracted new guests to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHLeisureTransportationSuccessShort"  >The publicity campaign featuring photos taken from Jeep&#xAE; vehicles has attracted more guests to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_JeepWithGuests"  >Take a photo of three or more guests riding in a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_JeepWithAnimals"  >While riding in a Jeep vehicle, take a photo of one animal species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_JeepWithAnimals2"  >While riding in a Jeep vehicle, take a photo of a second animal species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart1Photos"  >Endangered Animals Alliance - Photo Shoot</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart1"  >(Endangered Species Challenge) The Endangered Animals Alliance is offering your zoo a free endangered species that you don't currently have. However, the alliance wants proof that your zoo is committed to conserving endangered species. Provide the alliance with photos of three different endangered species from your zoo, and the alliance will give you a free animal. The animals must be happy for your photos to qualify!
		<br/>
   			Difficulty: Moderate			
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart1Short"  >Take photos of three different endangered species to receive a free animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart1Success"  >Your photos have convinced the Endangered Animals Alliance that your zoo is committed to protecting endangered species. The alliance has granted you an animal as a reward. You will find the %s crated near the entrance to your zoo. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart1SuccessShort"  >As a reward for taking photos of endangered species, you have been given a %s.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart1ThemePromo"  >Complete two endangered species challenges to unlock the endangered species themed objects!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart1FirstEndangeredAnimal"  >Take a photo of one happy endangered species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart1SecondEndangeredAnimal"  >Take a photo of a second happy endangered species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart1ThirdEndangeredAnimal"  >Take a photo of a third happy endangered species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart2Photos"  >Endangered Animals Alliance - Animal Enrichment</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart2"  >(Endangered Species Challenge) The Endangered Animals Alliance would like some photos of endangered species using enrichment objects, which it will post on its Web site. If you can provide the alliance with the right photos, your zoo will receive a free tire swing enrichment item as compensation. The alliance would like the following photos:
			<br/>         
		*  A giant sable antelope using a salt lick.  
			<br/>     
		*  A young Komodo dragon in a lookout post. 
			<br/>
		*  A gray wolf eating a beef shank.
			<p/>
   			Difficulty: Easy.				
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart2Short"  >Take the following photos:
			<br/>         
		*  A giant sable antelope using a salt lick.  
			<br/>     
		*  A young Komodo dragon in a lookout post. 
			<br/>
		*  A gray wolf eating a beef shank.
			<br/>			
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart2Success"  >Congratulations! The Endangered Animals Alliance loved your photos of endangered species using enrichment items, and they're giving your zoo a free tire swing enrichment item. You'll find the tire swing in a crate near the entrance to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart2SuccessShort"  >Your photos of endangered species using enrichment items earned you a free tire swing.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart2ThemePromo"  >Complete two endangered species challenges to unlock the endangered species themed objects!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart2GiantSableAntelope"  >Take a photo of a giant sable antelope using a salt lick.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart2KomodoDragon"  >Take a photo of a young Komodo dragon in a lookout post.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart2GrayWolf"  >Take a photo of a gray wolf eating a beef shank.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart3Photos"  >Endangered Animals Alliance - Animal Behaviors</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart3"  >(Endangered Species Challenge) The Endangered Animals Alliance wants your help in obtaining photos to publicize the alliance's next fundraising campaign. If you can provide photos of certain endangered species engaged in specific behaviors, the alliance will award you one of the rarest animals of all: the critically endangered Florida panther. Take the following photos:
					<br/>         
		*  A wolverine eating from a food dish.  
					<br/>     
		*  Two crested gibbons grooming each other. 
					<br/>
		*  A spectacled bear eating from a puya plant.
					<br/>
   			Difficulty: Moderate.			
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart3Short"  >Take the following photos:
					<br/>         
		*  A wolverine eating from a food dish.  
					<br/>     
		*  Two crested gibbons grooming each other. 
					<br/>
		*  A spectacled bear eating from a puya plant		
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart3Success"  >Good work! The Endangered Animals Alliance says your great photos of endangered species will help raise money during the next fundraising campaign. In recognition of everything you've done to help save endangered species, the alliance has awarded you a rare Florida panther. You'll find the panther in a crate near the entrance to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart3SuccessShort"  >Your photos of endangered species engaged in specific behaviors has earned you a rare Florida panther.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHEAAPart3ThemePromo"  >Complete two endangered species challenges to unlock the endangered species themed objects!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart3Wolverine"  >Take a photo of a wolverine eating from a food dish.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart3CrestedGibbon"  >Take a photo of two crested gibbons grooming each other.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_EAAPart3ThirdEndangeredAnimal"  >Take a photo of a spectacled bear eating from a puya plant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHDivaVisitPhotos"  >Diva Visit</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHDivaVisit"  >You just heard a hot rumor! Famous singer Dallas Samson, the star of stage, screen, and reality TV, is about to visit your zoo! If guests knew that celebrities like Dallas Samson visit your zoo, it would make your zoo more famous. When Dallas Samson visits your zoo, take the following photos as proof that she visited:
					<br/>         
		*  A photo of Dallas Samson eating or drinking.  
					<br/>     
		*  A photo of Dallas Samson viewing an animal. 
					<br/>
		*  A photo of Dallas Samson riding on a sky tram.
					<br/>
   			Difficulty: Moderate.			
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHDivaVisitShort"  >Take the following photos:
					<br/>         
		*  A photo of Dallas Samson eating or drinking.  
					<br/>     
		*  A photo of Dallas Samson viewing an animal. 
					<br/>
		*  A photo of Dallas Samson riding on a sky tram.		
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHDivaVisitSuccess"  >You rushed your photos of famous singer Dallas Samson to the local newspaper. The resulting good publicity has made your zoo more famous. Not only that, but all the guests currently in your zoo are now slightly happier. Everyone's thrilled to be visiting the star's favorite zoo!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHDivaVisitSuccessShort"  >The publicity from your celebrity photos has made your guests slightly happier and made your zoo more famous as well.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHDivaVisitFailure"  >Dallas Samson has left the zoo! Unfortunately, she left before you could get all the photos you needed.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHDivaVisitFailureShort"  >Dallas Samson left the zoo before you could get the photos you needed.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHDivaVisitDivaName"  >Dallas Samson</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_DivaVisitEatDrink"  >Take a photo of Dallas Samson eating or drinking.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_DivaVisitViewingAnimal"  >Take a photo of Dallas Samson viewing an animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_DivaVisitSkyTram"  >Take a photo of Dallas Samson riding on a sky tram.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_DivaVisitArrival"  >Famous singer Dallas Samson has entered your zoo!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHAntipodalWildlifePhotos"  >Antipodal Wildlife Endowment</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHAntipodalWildlife"  >The Antipodal Wildlife Endowment would like some photos of animals from the Southern Hemisphere for their promotional literature. If you can take the photos for them, AWE will present you with a very special reward: your own Australian koala! They would like the following photos:
			<br/>         
		*  A photo of a Galapagos giant tortoise egg.    
			<br/>     
		*  A photo of two Komodo dragons touching tongues. 
			<br/>
		*  A photo of two African wild dogs sleeping in a heap.
			<p/>
   			Difficulty: Hard		
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHAntipodalWildlifeShort"  >Take the following photos:
			<br/>         
		*  A photo of a Galapagos giant tortoise egg.    
			<br/>     
		*  A photo of two Komodo dragons touching tongues. 
			<br/>
		*  A photo of two African wild dogs sleeping in a heap.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHAntipodalWildlifeSuccess"  >Good work! The Antipodal Wildlife Association was pleased with your photos of animals from the Southern Hemisphere, and they have given you your very own koala! You'll find the koala in a crate near the entrance to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHAntipodalWildlifeSuccessShort"  >Your photos of animals from the Southern Hemisphere have earned you a free koala.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_AntipodalWildlifeGalapagosTortoise"  >Take a photo of a Galapagos giant tortoise egg.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_AntipodalWildlifeAfricanWildDog"  >Take a photo of two African wild dogs sleeping in a heap.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_AntipodalWildlifeKomodoDragon"  >Take a photo of two Komodo dragons touching tongues.</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
