<ZT2Strings>
   <alert>
      <sttformat>
         <font name="arial" size="10">%text%</font>
      </sttformat>
      <lttformat>
         <font name="arial" size="10">%text%</font>
      </lttformat>
      <save_game_message>
         <font name="arial" size="20">
            <b>Game Saved</b>
         </font>
      </save_game_message>
      <alert>
         <font name="arial" size="16">
            <color r="255" g="197" b="78">
               <b>%text%</b>
            </color>
         </font>
      </alert>
      <save_failed>Out of hard drive space. Unable to save game.</save_failed>
      <diskfull_operation_failure>Out of hard drive space. Unable to complete operation.</diskfull_operation_failure>
      <photo_save_failed>Out of hard drive space. Unable to save photo.</photo_save_failed>
      <download_save_failed>Out of hard drive space. Unable to complete download.</download_save_failed>
      <invalid_name_profile>Profile names must contain at least one letter or number.</invalid_name_profile>
      <invalid_name_save>File names must contain at least one letter or number.</invalid_name_save>
      <profile_exists>That profile already exists. Please choose a different name.</profile_exists>
      <album_exists>Duplicate or blank photo album names are not permitted. Please choose a different name.</album_exists>
      <profile_problem>There was a problem creating that profile. Please try a different name.</profile_problem>
      <save_failed_readonly>File is read-only. Unable to save game.</save_failed_readonly>
      <load_failed>File is corrupted or otherwise unreadable. Unable to load game.</load_failed>
      <skipped_entity_load>The save you loaded contains references to items not installed on your machine. As a result, you may notice missing objects, animals, or fences!</skipped_entity_load>
      <delete_failed>Unable to delete game.  The file may be read-only.</delete_failed>
      <options_save_failed>Unable to save user options.  The current profile may be invalid.</options_save_failed>
      <new_save_game>The save you are trying to load was created by a newer version of Zoo Tycoon 2 not supported by this version.</new_save_game>
      <old_save_game>The save you are trying to load is no longer supported by this version of Zoo Tycoon 2.</old_save_game>
   </alert>
   <error>
      <startup_error_title>Zoo Tycoon 2 Startup Error</startup_error_title>
      <init_config_info_failed>Error in call to InitConfigInformation.</init_config_info_failed>
      <d3d_create_failed>Failed to create Direct3D Object.</d3d_create_failed>
      <init_video_card_info_failed>Error in call to Config_InitVideoCardInfo.</init_video_card_info_failed>
      <enumerate_adapter_modes_failed>Failed to enumerate graphics adapter modes.</enumerate_adapter_modes_failed>
      <slow_processor>You need at least a 1.0 GHz processor for Zoo Tycoon 2 to run properly.  (%s MHz detected.)</slow_processor>
      <low_system_memory>You need at least %1s MB of system memory to run Zoo Tycoon 2.  (%2s MB detected.)</low_system_memory>
      <low_video_memory>You need at least %1s MB of video memory to run Zoo Tycoon 2.  (%2s MB detected.)</low_video_memory>
      <unsupported_graphics_adapter>Zoo Tycoon 2 does not support the %s graphics card.</unsupported_graphics_adapter>
      <prototype_graphics_adapter>The %s graphics card is a prototype card and may cause problems with Zoo Tycoon 2.</prototype_graphics_adapter>
      <invalid_graphics_driver>Your graphics driver is not valid for your operating system. Please contact your graphics card vendor for an updated driver.</invalid_graphics_driver>
      <old_graphics_driver>Your graphics driver may be too old to run Zoo Tycoon 2. Please contact your graphics card vendor for an updated driver.</old_graphics_driver>
      <invalid_sound_driver>Your sound driver is not valid for your operating system. Please contact your sound card vendor for an updated driver.</invalid_sound_driver>
      <old_sound_driver>Your sound driver may be too old to run Zoo Tycoon 2. Please contact your sound card vendor for an updated driver.</old_sound_driver>
      <renderer_create_failed>Zoo Tycoon 2 was unable to create a graphics renderer. Please contact your graphics card vendor to make sure you have the latest driver.</renderer_create_failed>
      <mm_not_installed>Zoo Tycoon 2 does not appear to be properly installed.  Please check your system settings and reinstall from the CD.</mm_not_installed>
   </error>
</ZT2Strings>
