<ZT2Strings>
 <zoopedia_alpineseaholly>
  <entry>Plant, Alpine Sea Holly</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/AlpineSeaHolly/AlpineSeaHolly_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
Alpine sea holly is a perennial plant that looks like a thistle. It blooms in mid- to late- summer with striking blue flowers and stems. Many consider Alpine sea holly to be one of the world's most beautiful blooming plants. Despite its popularity in gardens, the plant is endangered in its native habitat, the European Alps.
     </cell>
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_alpineseaholly>

 <zoopedia_bigbluestem>
  <entry>Plant, Big Bluestem</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/BigBluestem/BigBluestem_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
Bluestem is the common name for over 200 species of grasses named for the blue-green color of the young stems. Most bluestems are native to the tall grass prairies in the eastern half of North America, although some are native to Eurasia and northern Africa. They are often planted to restore native prairies or are grown as ornamental grasses.
     <p/>
Bluestems are perennials, which means they live for at least three years. They have solid stems unlike most grasses that have hollow stems. The flower, or spikelet, consists of two wheat-like kernels. The spikelets may attach directly to a narrow stem, forming a flowerhead called a spike, or they may attach to a short stalk that attaches to a narrow stem, forming a flowerhead called a raceme.
     <p/>
A common species known as big bluestem is 1 to 2 m (3 to 6 ft) tall, forms a robust clump, and blooms from August through November. The stems are often covered with downy fuzz and may branch near the top. The leaf blades are flat and up to 2 cm (0.8 in) long. The spikelet resembles the three-toed foot of a turkey—big bluestem is sometimes called turkeyfoot grass. The raceme is purplish and 5 to 10 cm (2 to 4 in) long. Big bluestem sometimes produces underground stems called rhizomes, from which new plants grow.     
     </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_bigbluestem>
 
 <zoopedia_evergreenoak>
  <entry>Tree, Evergreen Oak</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/EvergreenOak/Tree_EvergreenOak_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
Oak is the common name for a large genus of hardwood trees that are widespread in the North Temperate Zone. The oak genus contains about 450 species. Oaks are distinguished from the other ten or so genera in the beech family, to which the oak genus belongs, by various technical characteristics of their minute, clustered flowers, but they are easily recognized by their distinctive fruit, the acorn. The related tan oak, one species of which occurs in the coastal ranges of California and Oregon, also produces an acorn. The tan oak differs from the oak genus in its upright rather than hanging male flower clusters.
    <p/>
About 60 species of oak occur in the United States and Canada, with about 150 additional species in Mexico. They grow in a variety of habitats, from seacoasts to high mountain slopes and from wet lowlands to high, dry mesas. Flowering occurs in the spring, before the new leaves appear, and large quantities of pollen are shed into the wind. The trees may be deciduous (losing their leaves in the fall) or evergreen. Most eastern United States species are deciduous—the live oak of the southeastern coastal plain being a notable exception—whereas the western United States has both many evergreen and many deciduous species.    
    <p/>
Oaks produce durable, tough wood and are important lumber trees. The wood is used in cabinetry and barrel making and as flooring and veneers. Corks are made from the thick, spongy bark of the cork oak, which occurs in the Mediterranean region. Several species yield tannins, which are used in the leather-tanning industry, and others yield dyes from their bark. Oaks are of some horticultural importance, but because most are slow growing, they are more often planted in public parks and gardens than in private lawns. Scarlet oak, willow oak, and pin oak, however, are moderate to fast-growing species that are well suited to both purposes.    
            <p/>
Contributed By:
            <br/>
Marshall R. Crosby
    </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>  
 </zoopedia_evergreenoak>
 
 <zoopedia_giantsequoia>
  <entry>Tree, Giant Sequoia</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/GiantSequoia/Tree_GiantSequoia_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
The giant sequoia, Sequoiadendron giganteum, is the most massive of all living forms, growing to heights of 83 m (272 ft). It is believed to live 2400 to 4000 years, making it one of the longest living species on earth.
     <p/>
The giant sequoia, or "big tree," is found in a narrow strip about 300 km (about 200 mi) long on the western slopes of the Sierra Nevada range at elevations between about 900 and 2400 m (about 3000 and 8000 ft). It is the most massive of all living forms. The largest specimen, the General Sherman Tree in Sequoia National Park, is 84 m (275 ft) tall, has a diameter of 11.1 m (36.4 ft) at the base, and was estimated in the early 1990s to weigh about 2500 metric tons. Other trees range from 46 to 99 m (150 to 325 ft) in height, with diameters up to 9 m (30 ft). A count of annual rings on stumps has verified ages as great as 2300 years. Some living trees, however, are believed to be close to 4000 years old.     
     <p/>
The leaves of the giant sequoia are scalelike and lie close to the branches. The bark of the trunk is fluted and is spongy in texture; in large trees it reaches a thickness of 60 cm (2 ft). The wood is light, coarse-grained, and highly resistant to insects and fire. Most of the giant sequoia groves are included within the National Park System or are otherwise under government protection--cutting of the big trees is prohibited.     
     </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>  
 </zoopedia_giantsequoia>
 
 <zoopedia_joshuatree>
  <entry>Tree, Joshua</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/JoshuaTree/JoshuaTree_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
The Joshua tree is found in the Mojave Desert of the southwestern United States and grows to a height of 9 m (30 ft). The tree was so named because its branches recall the arm of the prophet Joshua as he pointed, spear in hand, to the city of Ai, in ancient Greece.
     <p/>
The Joshua tree is a member of the Yucca family, a genus of stiff-leaved, evergreen shrubs and trees containing about 30 species, which are native to North America and the West Indies. Several types are widely cultivated for their ornamental appearance and attractive flowers. The spearlike leaves are borne in tufts, and from the center of the tuft grows the large flower stalk, which bears a cluster of bell-shaped, drooping blossoms. Pollination rarely occurs except with the aid of the yucca moth.
     <p/>
The coarse fibers obtained from the stem and foliage of many yucca plants were used in the manufacture of cordage. Many yuccas of the southeastern United States have grasslike leaves, known as bear grass, which are used as filling for chair cushions and pillows. The roots of some species yield a fatty substance used in some countries as a soap. The name yucca is commonly but incorrectly applied to the date yucca.     
     </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2005 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>  
 </zoopedia_joshuatree>

 <zoopedia_ladyfern>
  <entry>Plant, Lady Fern</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/LadyFern/LadyFern_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
Lady fern is the common name of a genus of about 100 species of true ferns, mostly natives of warm climates. The common lady fern is widely found in the north temperate zone, growing in large masses in open woods. Its soft, finely cut foliage reaches 91 to 122 cm (36 to 48 in) in height. Several other species are cultivated under glass or in gardens for their deeply cut or variegated foliage.
     </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_ladyfern>
 
 <zoopedia_pinkladyslipper>
  <entry>Plant, Pink Lady's Slipper</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/PinkLadySlipper/PinkLadySlipper_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
Pink Lady’s Slipper, also known as moccasin flower, is the common name for several related genera of orchids that share the characteristics of large, ridged leaves and either one or a few slipper-shaped flowers borne on stalks above them. The expanded, saclike "slipper" is the lip of the flower, which is unusual among orchids in having two fertile anthers (pollen-bearing parts of the plant).
     <p/>
North American lady's slippers are members of a genus of some 50 species that also occurs in Eurasia. The flowers referred to as cypripediums by florists belong to two related genera: one with about 60 species native to tropical Asia; and the other with about 12 species native to South and Central America. Their cultivation requires greenhouse conditions. Two other, unrelated orchids are also called lady's slippers because of the shape of their flowers.     
     <p/>
Contributed By:
            <br/>
Marshall R. Crosby     
     </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>  
 </zoopedia_pinkladyslipper>
 
 <zoopedia_puyaplant>
  <entry>Plant, Puya</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Puya/Puya_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
There are more than 160 species of puya plant, most of which are native to the Andes region of South America. During the spring, puya plants send up great spikes covered with blossoms. This makes the puya plant a favorite of nectar-drinking birds, as well as of the omnivorous spectacled bear.
     </cell>
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>  
 </zoopedia_puyaplant>
 
 <zoopedia_buroak>
  <entry>Tree, Bur Oak</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/BurOak/BurOak_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
 The bur oak, also known as the mossy-cup oak, is known for its massive size and is considered to be one of the most majestic trees growing in North America.
     <p/>
 Oak is the common name for a large genus of hardwood trees that are widespread in the North Temperate Zone. The oak genus contains about 450 species. Oaks are distinguished from the other ten or so genera in the beech family, to which the oak genus belongs, by various technical characteristics of their minute, clustered flowers, but they are easily recognized by their distinctive fruit, the acorn. The related tan oak, one species of which occurs in the coastal ranges of California and Oregon, also produces an acorn. The tan oak differs from the oak genus in its upright rather than hanging male flower clusters.
     <p/>
 About 60 species of oak occur in the United States and Canada, with about 150 additional species in Mexico. They grow in a variety of habitats, from seacoasts to high mountain slopes and from wet lowlands to high, dry mesas. Flowering occurs in the spring, before the new leaves appear, and large quantities of pollen are shed into the wind. The trees may be deciduous (losing their leaves in the fall) or evergreen. Most eastern United States species are deciduous—the live oak of the southeastern coastal plain being a notable exception—whereas the western United States has both many evergreen and many deciduous species.
    <p/>
 Oaks produce durable, tough wood and are important lumber trees. The wood is used in cabinetry and barrel making and as flooring and veneers. Corks are made from the thick, spongy bark of the cork oak, which occurs in the Mediterranean region. Several species yield tannins, which are used in the leather-tanning industry, and others yield dyes from their bark. Oaks are of some horticultural importance, but because most are slow growing, they are more often planted in public parks and gardens than in private lawns. Scarlet oak, willow oak, and pin oak, however, are moderate to fast-growing species that are well suited to both purposes.
      <p/>
 Contributed By:
             <br/>
Marshall R. Crosby  
    </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_buroak>
 
 <zoopedia_feathertopwiregrass>
  <entry>Plant, Feathertop Wiregrass</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/FeathertopWiregrass/FeathertopWiregrass_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
Feathertop wiregrass is a shallow-rooted grass that is native to central and northern Australia. It is unpopular with both wool and beef ranchers in Australia because it inhibits the growth of more productive grazing grasses and its dart-like seeds get stuck in wool. Although it will dry out under drought conditions, it is also often the victim of controlled burning.
     </cell>
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_feathertopwiregrass>
 
 <zoopedia_goldenbarrelcactus>
  <entry>Plant, Golden Barrel Cactus</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/GoldenBarrelCactus/GoldenBarrelCactus_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
The golden barrel cactus, a native of central Mexico, is one of the most sought-after members of the cactus family.
     <p/>
Cactus is the common name for the family comprising a peculiar group of spiny, fleshy plants native to America. The family contains about 1650 species, most of which are adapted to arid climates. The fruits of cacti are important sources of food and drink in many areas to which they are native. Because cacti require little care and exhibit bizarre forms, they are popular for home cultivation and are coming under increasing pressure as a result. More than 17 kinds of cacti, including the golden barrel cactus, now face extinction because of plundering by avid collectors and professional poachers, especially in the southwestern United States and northern Mexico.
     <p/>
Cactus plants usually consist of spiny stems and roots. Leaves are greatly reduced or entirely absent. Only in two genera are fully formed leaves present. The stems of cacti are usually swollen and fleshy, adapted to water storage, and many are shaped in ways that cause rain to flow directly to the root system for absorption. The roots form extensive systems near the soil surface, assuring that a given plant will absorb the maximum amount of water from a wide area; plants in deserts are usually widely spaced.
     <p/>
The most distinctive vegetative feature of cacti is the areoles, specialized areas on the stems on which stiff, sharp spines usually grow. Some cacti lack spines but have hairs or sharp, barbed structures called glocids on the areoles. Areoles develop from lateral buds on the stems and appear to represent highly specialized branches.
     <p/>
The flowers of cacti are often large and showy and occur singly rather than in clusters of several flowers. The perianth (floral tube) does not consist of sharply differentiated sepals and petals, but rather of a series of bracts (modified leaves), which gradually grade into sepals and finally into showy petals. The flowers have many stamens; the ovary is inferior and fused to the perianth. The fruits are often brightly colored and fleshy.
     <p/>
Most of the 130 or so genera of cacti are found in cultivation, the small, slow-growing species being most popular because of their variety in shapes, colors, and spines. One of the best-known is a group containing beautiful night-blooming flowers and the familiar saguaro plant. In some classifications, this group is split into as many as 10 separate genera. Still more widely grown is the group containing the Christmas cactus. Species of this group, which naturally occur as epiphytes (air plants) in tropical rain forests, do not fit the popular idea of cacti as squat, fleshy plants of desert regions. Examination of their stems, however, reveals the presence of the cactus family’s unique areoles; their flowers have the typical cactus features.
     <p/>
Many groups of plants that are unrelated to cacti have also adapted to survive in arid regions and often resemble cacti in appearance. These offer examples of parallel evolution: Unrelated organisms subjected to similar environmental stresses often evolve similar anatomical and functional characteristics. For example, many spurges that grow in dry parts of Africa, where cacti are not found, exhibit leafless, spiny, fleshy stems.
     <p/>
Contributed By:
     <br/>
Marshall R. Crosby   
     </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_goldenbarrelcactus>
 
 <zoopedia_redoatgrass>
  <entry>Plant, Red Oat Grass</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/RedOatGrass/RedOatGrass_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
Red oat grass, themeda triandra, is a perennial grass that is native to Australia. Also known as kangaroo grass, it grows throughout the Australian continent, from the interior to the mountains to the coast.
     <p/>
The native Aboriginal people of Australia used kangaroo grass to weave fishing nets, and many people in the high country areas of New South Wales collect the kangaroo grass seeds to grind into flour and then bake into cakes.
     <p/>
Kangaroo grass is both highly drought tolerant and highly heat tolerant, and it is a popular form of browse feed for many native Australian animals.
     </cell>
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_redoatgrass>
 
 <zoopedia_shepardstree>
  <entry>Tree, Shepherd's Tree</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/ShepardsTree/ShepardsTree_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
The shepherd's tree is a small evergreen tree that is highly prized by African farmers for its edible roots, which livestock can eat in times of famine. These roots give the tree its alternate name, "famine food." The tree also provides shelter, shade, and browsing to the animals of southern Africa, particularly in the Kalahari Desert.
     </cell>
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_shepardstree>
 
 <zoopedia_yellowipetree>
  <entry>Tree, Yellow Ipe</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/YellowIpeTree/YellowIpeTree_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">
The yellow ipe tree, also known as the trumpet tree, is one of the most important trees growing in the dense Amazon Forest of South America.
     <p/>
Trumpet tree is the common name for a genus of about 100 species of shrubs or trees with large, showy, trumpet-shaped flowers. Native to the tropical Americas, trumpet trees are widely cultivated as ornamentals in tropical and subtropical regions around the world. They grow best in deep, fertile soil and full sun.
     <p/>
The yellow ipe tree, or tree of gold, is native to Paraguay, Argentina, and Brazil. It attains heights of 8 m (26 ft). The silvery compound leaves (leaves that consist of several leaflets arranged along a central stem) have five to seven leaflets, each one 6 to 18 cm (2.5 to 7 in) long. The golden yellow flowers can reach 6.25 cm (2.5 in) in length.
     <p/>
The yellow ipe is also the official symbol of Brazil. The yellow ipe's beautiful flowers that blossom in the middle of the dry season are a symbol of hope to many Brazilians when everything else looks dry and bleak.
     </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_yellowipetree>
 
 <zoopedia_pricklypearcactus>
  <entry>Plant, Prickly Pear Cactus</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/PricklyPearCactus/PricklyPear_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">     
Prickly pear is the common name for plants of a genus of the cactus family. The plants are characterized by flat-jointed stems covered with small clusters of stiff hairs called glochids, and usually also spines. The flowers are commonly yellow and develop into warty, pear-shaped edible fruits. The most important species are the tuna and the Indian fig. These species originated in American subtropical and tropical areas, and they have been naturalized in tropical regions throughout the world. As forage for cattle, prickly pears are cultivated in arid lands of the western United States.
   <p/>
Although native to the tropical and subtropical regions of the southwestern United States, Baja California, and the Sonoran Desert region of Mexico, the prickly pear cactus has been introduced throughout dry, arid regions of the world. The flowers of the prickly pear produce edible fruit suitable for human consumption.
    </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_pricklypearcactus>
 
 <zoopedia_scythianlamb>
  <entry>Plant, Scythian Lamb</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities\objects\foliage\ScythianLamb\ScythianLamb_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">     
Native to Asia, the Scythian lamb is a tree fern that is known for having dense matted hairs and a wooly-skinned rootstock that resembles a lamb.
   <p/>
Tree ferns, tall ferns that resemble a tree, are found in warm regions throughout the world. The tree fern has a woody trunk, known as a caudex, which is tall and slender in some species, and somewhat stout in others. At the top of the trunk is a rosette of large, graceful, finely cut leaves, sometimes 3 m (10 ft) in length. Many tree ferns reach 4.6 to 9 m (15 to 30 ft) in height. Species of the genus Cyathea may exceed 15 m (50 ft). Tree ferns are a beautiful feature of tropical vegetation, and several species are planted in conservatories. 
	 </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_scythianlamb>
 
 <zoopedia_duriantree>
  <entry>Tree, Durian</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/DurianTree/DurianTree_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">     
Durian tree is the common name for an evergreen tree (one that retains its foliage throughout the year) native to the hot, humid rain forests of Southeast Asia, where it is cultivated for its fruit. The common name is derived from the Malayan word for the tree’s fruit, duryon.
   <p/>
The durian tree usually grows to heights of 24 to 30 m (80 to 100 ft), although it has been known to grow to 45 m (150 ft). The leaves, up to 17.5 cm (7 in) long, have silver- or copper-colored scales on the lower surface. The flowers, about 5 cm (about 2 in) long, have white, yellow, or pink petals and grow in clusters. The fruit requires about three months to develop; when it is ripe it drops from the tree.
   <p/>
The durian fruit is often called the world’s most dangerous fruit. It is round or egg shaped and usually weighs 2.8 to 3.5 kg (6 to 8 lb). Its thick rind is green or yellowish and covered with hard, sharp spines. The fruit must be handled by its stalk to avoid injury from the spines. A human or animal hit by a falling durian can be seriously injured or even killed. Inside the fruit are one to four large seeds, each up to 3.5 cm (1.3 in) long, that are edible when roasted, fried, or boiled. The rest of the fruit consists of a custardlike pulp that is foul smelling but very tasty. The pulp is usually eaten fresh but is also added to cakes, ice cream, and other foods. Elephants, tigers, rhinoceroses, and other wild animals are attracted by the odor of ripe durians and compete for fallen fruit.
    </cell>    
    </cell>   
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_duriantree>
 
 <zoopedia_lingonberry>
  <entry>Plant, Lingonberry</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Lingonberry/Lingonberry_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">     
The lingonberry is the fruit of the mountain cranberry.
   <p/>
Thick boreal coniferous forests are found in coastal regions and in the valleys of eastern and central Norway. These forests are dominated by Scotch pine and Norway spruce, but also contain birch, alder, aspen, and mountain ash. Wild berries, such as the blueberry, lingonberry, and cloudberry, grow in most woodland areas.
   <p/>
Cranberry is the common name for several species of low vines of a genus of the heath family, and for their small, sour, seedy fruit. The plants, which belong to the same genus as the blueberry, have drooping, pink flowers and small, thick, evergreen leaves. The small, or European, cranberry grows wild in marshlands of temperate and colder regions of Europe and North America. The large, or American, cranberry is cultivated in the northeastern United States in sand-covered bogs that can be flooded or drained at will. Flooding protects the vines from frosts and freezing weather and destroys insect pests. Most of the cranberry crop produced in the United States each year is canned as sauce or jelly or bottled as juice. lingonberry, or mountain cranberry, is common in both Europe and North America. It is gathered and sold in considerable quantity but is rarely cultivated. The highbush cranberry, with its clusters of white flowers followed by red berries, is a shrub of the honeysuckle family. Its fruit is sometimes used as a substitute for cranberries.
    </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_lingonberry>
 
 <zoopedia_greenpitcherplant>
  <entry>Plant, Green Pitcher Plant</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/GreenPitcherPlant/GreenPitcherPlant_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">     
The green pitcher plant is a critically endangered carnivorous plant that grows mainly in sandy bogs in the southern United States.
<p/>
Pitcher plant is the common name for three families of flowering dicot plants, members of which have leaves modified as pitchers for trapping and digesting insects. The entire leaves of all these plants are tubular and hollow and lined with downward-pointing hairs. When an insect enters, it cannot climb back out against the hairs and ultimately falls to the bottom of the leaf, to be digested by juices contained there. Pitcher plants typically occur in poor soils and depend partly on nutrients obtained from the digested insects.
<p/>
Contributed By:
<br/>
Marshall R. Crosby
    </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_greenpitcherplant>
 
 <zoopedia_labradortea>
  <entry>Plant, Labrador Tea</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/LabradorTea/LabradorTea_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">     
Labrador tea is a low shrub of the heath family. Six species are native chiefly to the arctic regions of North America and one to Asia. The Labrador tea shrub typically stands from 1 to 2 m (3 to 6 ft) tall, with evergreen leaves that are rusty on the under side. The small white flowers appear in May and June in showy terminal clusters. The leaves, which are aromatic when bruised, contain oil that has narcotic properties. During the American Revolution these leaves were used as a tea substitute. The western Labrador tea is poisonous to sheep. The common Labrador tea is widespread in northern North America.
    </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_labradortea>
 
 <zoopedia_sydneybluegum>
  <entry>Tree, Sydney Blue Gum</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/SydneyBlueGum/SydneyBlueGum_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">     
Sydney blue gum is the common name for eucalyptus saligna, a type of eucalyptus tree.
   <p/>
Eucalyptus is the name for a genus of trees and some shrubs of the myrtle family. This genus, which includes over 800 species, forms the preponderant vegetation and most valuable timber trees of western Australian forests. Eucalyptus trees are characterized by leathery, whitish leaves that hang vertically, their edges facing the sun, and their ragged bark and peculiar aroma. Some trees in the genus are among the tallest trees known. One specimen of mountain ash with a height of at least 97 m (at least 318 ft) was found near Melbourne, Australia.
   <p/>
Many species are known as gum trees because of their resinous exudations. Among these are the Sydney blue gum and the cider gum, the lumber of which is widely used. Other species are known as stringybarks because of their fibrous inner bark. The peppermint trees, black peppermint and Sydney peppermint, are also included in this group. The ironbarks have hard gray bark and yield good timber. Botany Bay kino, a dark red, odorless gum employed as an astringent and a hemostatic drug and for tanning and dyeing, is derived from the ironbarks. The bloodwoods have reddish wood and also yield Botany Bay kino. Dragon's blood, tannin, oils, dyes, tars, and acids are yielded by other species of eucalyptus. 
    </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_sydneybluegum>
 
 <zoopedia_perepattree>
  <entry>Tree, Perepat</entry>
  <text>
   <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
    <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
     <cell width="150">
      <img src="entities/objects/foliage/PerepatTree/PerepatTree_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
     </cell>
     <cell pady="15" width="400">     
The Perepat mangrove is a tree that plays a key role in the development of mud flats and mangrove forests on the coast of Malaysia. The extensive root systems help form a barrier to waves and tides, helping to form the mangrove forest, a common habitat for the proboscis monkey.
   <p/>
Mangrove is the common name applied to several kinds of tropical flowering plants that are members of three different families. Mangroves are trees or shrubs that have the common trait of growing in shallow and muddy salt water or brackish waters, especially along quiet shorelines and in estuaries. Typically they produce tangled masses of arching roots that are exposed during low tides. Some mangrove roots extend above the water. These specialized vertical branches, called pneumatophores, act as aerating organs. The most common and most important species, the red mangrove, is so named because of its reddish wood. It has been exploited as a source of charcoal and of tannins, which are used in preparing leather. Its seeds are unusual in that they germinate while still on the tree, sprouting seedlings that grow up to 30 cm (12 in) long. The seedlings are cigar-shaped and heavier at the root end than at the leafy end. Upon falling, they tend to plant themselves in the mud below the parent tree. Red, white, and button mangroves occur in southern Florida and in other tropical areas. The black mangrove is a member of the verbena family.
   <p/>
Contributed By:
<br/>
Marshall R. Crosby
   <p/>
    </cell>
    </cell>
    <p/>
    <cell width="260"/>
    <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry"><u><color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2005.</color></u></a> (C) 1993-2004 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
    </cell>
   </color>
  </text>
 </zoopedia_perepattree>
 
</ZT2Strings>