	<ZT2Strings>
   <Challengetext>

      <CHGenericChallenge>Finally, if the animal meets misfortune while in your care and cannot be returned to its owner, you will be forced to pay a %s penalty. Difficulty: Moderate</CHGenericChallenge>
      <CHGenericChallengeShort>Breed the animal loaned to you within a two-month period. </CHGenericChallengeShort>
      <CHGenericChallengeSuccessShort>You successfully bred the animal loaned to your zoo. The animal and baby are yours to keep, and your fee has been refunded.</CHGenericChallengeSuccessShort>
      <CHGenericChallengeSuccess>Congratulations! You have successfully bred the animal loaned to you. The animal and baby are yours to keep, and your initial fee has been refunded.</CHGenericChallengeSuccess>
      <CHGenericChallengeFailureShort>You were unable to successfully breed the animal loaned to your zoo. It has been returned to its owner.</CHGenericChallengeFailureShort>
      <CHGenericChallengeFailure>The loan period has expired and the animal has been returned to its owner. Perhaps you can try again later with better results. </CHGenericChallengeFailure>
      <CHGenericChallengeBadFailureShort>The animal loaned to you could not be returned to its owner! You've had to pay a penalty.</CHGenericChallengeBadFailureShort>
      <CHGenericChallengeBadFailure>The animal loaned to you has met misfortune and cannot be returned to the owner! According to the terms of your agreement, %s has been deducted from your account.</CHGenericChallengeBadFailure>

      <CHMayorsChallenge>The local mayor has issued a challenge to your new zoo. If you can acquire a single %s during the next month, the city will award you a cash grant of $750. If you fail, though, the bad publicity will slightly reduce the number of guests who visit your zoo. Difficulty: Easy</CHMayorsChallenge>
      <CHMayorsChallengeShort>Acquire one %s within a one-month period.</CHMayorsChallengeShort>
      <CHMayorsChallengeSuccessShort>You've acquired the %s for your zoo, and the city has given you a $750 reward. The publicity has made your zoo more famous!</CHMayorsChallengeSuccessShort>
      <CHMayorsChallengeSuccess>Well done! You acquired your %s before the one-month deadline. The city has awarded you $750 to help get your zoo started, and the resulting press coverage has made your zoo more famous.</CHMayorsChallengeSuccess>
      <CHMayorsChallengeFailureShort>You were unable to obtain the %s before the deadline. The resulting bad publicity has slightly reduced the number of guests who visit your zoo for the next month.</CHMayorsChallengeFailureShort>
      <CHMayorsChallengeFailure>Unfortunately, you weren't able to obtain the %s before the one-month deadline. Not only have you failed to qualify for the cash grant, but negative press coverage of the whole affair has discouraged some guests from visiting your zoo. You will have slightly fewer guests than normal for the next month.</CHMayorsChallengeFailure>
      
      <CHVargasCheesecake>The Vargas Cheesecake Company is considering selling their delicious cheesecakes in your new zoo, but first they want proof that your zoo attracts guests with money to spend. If you can raise $250 of food and drink revenue, the Vargas Cheesecake Company will give you a free cheesecake cart to place in your zoo. 
			<br/>
   			Difficulty: Easy</CHVargasCheesecake>
      <CHVargasCheesecakeShort>Raise $250 in food and drink revenue during the month and receive a free cheesecake cart.</CHVargasCheesecakeShort>
      <CHVargasCheesecakeSuccessShort>You raised more than $250 in food and drink revenue, so the Vargas Cheesecake Company has awarded you a free cheesecake cart.</CHVargasCheesecakeSuccessShort>
      <CHVargasCheesecakeSuccess>Well done! You've raised more than $250 in food and drink revenue. That convinced the Vargas Cheesecake Company that their product will sell well in your facility, and they've given you a free cheesecake cart to place in your zoo. You'll find it in a crate near your zoo entrance.</CHVargasCheesecakeSuccess>
      <CHVargasCheesecakeFailureShort>You failed to raise $250 in food and drink revenue during the month, so you will not receive a free cheesecake cart.</CHVargasCheesecakeFailureShort>
      <CHVargasCheesecakeFailure>Too bad! A month has gone by and you still haven't raised $250 in food and drink revenue. As a result, the Vargas Cheesecake Company doesn't believe their product will sell well in your zoo. You've missed your chance to get a free cheesecake cart.</CHVargasCheesecakeFailure>

      <CHAcmeAmusements>Acme Amusements Inc. is running a promotion this month. They would like to give your zoo a free sample of one of their high-quality children's rides. However, they only give free samples to established zoos with a proven track record of guest donations. Earn $1,000 in donations during the next month and Acme Amusements will give you a free rhino bouncy ride. 
			<br/>
   			Difficulty: Easy</CHAcmeAmusements>
      <CHAcmeAmusementsShort>Raise $1,000 in donations during the month and receive a free rhino bouncy ride.</CHAcmeAmusementsShort>
      <CHAcmeAmusementsSuccessShort>Acme Amusements, Inc. gave you a free rhino bouncy ride after you raised more than $1,000 in donations.</CHAcmeAmusementsSuccessShort>
      <CHAcmeAmusementsSuccess>You raised more than $1,000 in donations during the month, so Acme Amusements, Inc. has sent you a rhino bouncy ride as a free sample of their merchandise. Look for it in a crate near your zoo entrance.</CHAcmeAmusementsSuccess>
      <CHAcmeAmusementsFailureShort>You failed to raise more than $1,000 in donations during the month, and you do not qualify to receive a free rhino bouncy ride.</CHAcmeAmusementsFailureShort>
      <CHAcmeAmusementsFailure>A month has gone by and you still haven't raised $1,000 in donations. Unfortunately, Acme Amusement's free sample promotion has ended. It looks like you missed your opportunity to get a free rhino bouncy ride.</CHAcmeAmusementsFailure>

      <CHRenovationInitiative>Your guests are growing bored with your zoo's drab look! They're especially tired of seeing all those chain link fences. If you can upgrade all the chain link fence in your zoo to something different within the next month, you'll be rewarded with extra guests and increased zoo fame. But if you have any chain link fence left in your zoo after the month is over, slightly fewer guests will visit your zoo in the month following! 
      <br/>      
      Difficulty: Variable</CHRenovationInitiative>
      <CHRenovationInitiativeShort>Replace all of the chain link fence in your zoo within a month.</CHRenovationInitiativeShort>
      <CHRenovationInitiativeSuccessShort>You removed all of the chain link fence from your zoo! Extra guests and increased zoo fame are your reward.</CHRenovationInitiativeSuccessShort>
      <CHRenovationInitiativeSuccess>Good work! Replacing all of your chain link fence has really freshened your zoo's appearance. New guests have arrived to check out your new look and your zoo has become more famous.</CHRenovationInitiativeSuccess>
      <CHRenovationInitiativeFailureShort>You failed to replace all of the chain link fence in your zoo. As a consequence, slightly fewer guests will visit your zoo during the next month.</CHRenovationInitiativeFailureShort>
      <CHRenovationInitiativeFailure>A month has passed and you still have chain link fence in your zoo. Your guests have grown tired of your zoo's drab look, and as a result you'll see fewer guests over the next month.</CHRenovationInitiativeFailure>

      <CHDisasterRelief>A small earthquake has struck your zoo! Fortunately, none of your guests or animals was hurt. However, the quake has destroyed some of your fences and alarmed the animals. The Disaster Relief Fund has offered you an aid package to reimburse you for the broken fences. Once you have replaced or removed all broken fences in your zoo, the fund will grant you %s in cash. Difficulty: Moderate</CHDisasterRelief>
      <CHDisasterReliefShort>Replace or remove all of the broken fences in your zoo to receive an aid grant.</CHDisasterReliefShort>
      <CHDisasterReliefSuccessShort>The Disaster Relief Fund awarded you an aid grant after you removed the broken fences from your zoo.</CHDisasterReliefSuccessShort>
      <CHDisasterReliefSuccess>Your zoo has recovered from the earthquake and things are returning to normal. The Disaster Relief Fund has given you a grant of %s to compensate you for the cost of cleaning up your broken fences.</CHDisasterReliefSuccess>
      <CHDisasterReliefFailureShort>Sorry, you waited too long to replace your broken fences and you're no longer eligible for disaster relief.</CHDisasterReliefFailureShort>
      <CHDisasterReliefFailure>Months have passed and you still haven't cleaned up the earthquake damage! Unfortunately, the deadline for receiving aid from the Disaster Relief Fund has passed. You are no longer eligible to receive a grant.</CHDisasterReliefFailure>
      
      <CHAnimalAssistance>(Endangered Species Challenge) The Animal Assistance Association has created an aggressive program to encourage breeding endangered species. If you can breed three different endangered species within two months, the association will pay you a breeding fee as a reward. The amount of the breeding fee will depend on the species you breed. 
      <br/>      
      Difficulty: Moderate</CHAnimalAssistance>
      <CHAnimalAssistanceShort>Breed three different endangered species within a two-month period.</CHAnimalAssistanceShort>
      <CHAnimalAssistanceSuccessShort>You successfully bred three different endangered species and received a breeding fee as a reward.</CHAnimalAssistanceSuccessShort>
      <CHAnimalAssistanceSuccess>Well done! You have bred three different endangered species. In recognition of your achievement in helping to preserve the animals, the Animal Assistance Association has given you a grant!</CHAnimalAssistanceSuccess>
      <CHAnimalAssistanceFailureShort>You were unable to breed three endangered species in two months, so you failed to qualify for the breeding fee program.</CHAnimalAssistanceFailureShort>
      <CHAnimalAssistanceFailure>Two months have passed and you have not been able to breed three different endangered species. The Animal Assistance Association has informed you that your zoo is no longer eligible for their breeding fee program. Better luck next time!</CHAnimalAssistanceFailure>
      <CHAnimalAssistanceOneBred>Congratulations! You have bred one endangered species. Breed two more different species to receive a breeding fee from the Animal Assistance Association.</CHAnimalAssistanceOneBred>
      <CHAnimalAssistanceTwoBred>Good work! You have bred a second endangered species. Breed one more species to receive a breeding fee from the Animal Assistance Association.</CHAnimalAssistanceTwoBred>
      <CHAnimalAssistanceThemePromo>Complete two Endangered Species challenges to unlock the Endangered-Species-Themed objects!</CHAnimalAssistanceThemePromo>      
      
      <CHCompuglobal>(Endangered Species Challenge) Compuglobal International, a major multinational corporation, is considering giving your zoo their annual Endangered Species Preservation Grant. Compuglobal will be sending three of its top executives to your zoo so they can evaluate it. If the executives view at least three different endangered species during their visit, then the $10,000 grant will be yours! (Hint: Keep the executives happy during their visit. If they become unhappy they may leave your zoo before viewing your endangered species.)
      <br/>
      Difficulty: Moderate</CHCompuglobal>
      <CHCompuglobalShort>If the Compuglobal executives visiting your zoo see three different endangered species, you will receive a grant of $10,000.</CHCompuglobalShort>
      <CHCompuglobalSuccessShort>You received a $10,000 grant because the Compuglobal executives saw three or more endangered species at your zoo.</CHCompuglobalSuccessShort>
      <CHCompuglobalSuccess>The Compuglobal executives have seen three or more endangered species! They were impressed with the variety of endangered species displayed in your zoo and have presented you with Compuglobal's Endangered Species Preservation Grant of $10,000.</CHCompuglobalSuccess>
      <CHCompuglobalFailureShort>The Compuglobal executives left without seeing three different endangered animal species. You did not receive the $10,000 grant.</CHCompuglobalFailureShort>
      <CHCompuglobalFailure>The Compuglobal executives didn't see three different endangered species before leaving. They're disappointed that your zoo hasn't made a stronger commitment to preserving endangered species. Your zoo will not receive Compuglobal's $10,000 Endangered Species Preservation Grant.</CHCompuglobalFailure>
      <CHCompuglobalArrival>The three Compuglobal executives have arrived at your zoo!</CHCompuglobalArrival>
      <CHCompuglobalOneSeen>So far, the Compuglobal executives have seen only one endangered species.</CHCompuglobalOneSeen>
      <CHCompuglobalTwoSeen>So far the Compuglobal executives have seen only two different endangered species. If they see one more endangered species, you will receive a $10,000 grant!</CHCompuglobalTwoSeen>
      <CHCompuglobalOneGone>One of the Compuglobal executives has left the zoo!</CHCompuglobalOneGone>
      <CHCompuglobalTwoGone>A second Compuglobal executive has left the zoo!</CHCompuglobalTwoGone>
      <CHCompuglobalThemePromo>Complete two Endangered Species challenges to unlock the Endangered-Species-Themed objects!</CHCompuglobalThemePromo>
      <CHCompuglobalExecutiveName>Compuglobal Executive</CHCompuglobalExecutiveName>
      <CHCompuglobalExecutiveName2>Compuglobal Executive 2</CHCompuglobalExecutiveName2>
      <CHCompuglobalExecutiveName3>Compuglobal Executive 3</CHCompuglobalExecutiveName3>      

      <CHAlternateTransport>The Alternate Transport Alliance wants to nationally publicize your zoo as a showcase for the transportation of the future--the clean, efficient sky tram. The Alliance has issued the following challenge: if you agree to build a sky tram system, the alliance will give you a $5,000 grant right now. If you transport 50 guests on your sky tram within the next two months, the alliance will give you another $5,000 after two months. However, if you fail to transport 50 guests within the allotted time, the resulting bad publicity will cause attendance at your zoo to decline slightly.  
      <br/>
      Difficulty: Hard</CHAlternateTransport>
      <CHAlternateTransportShort>Transport 50 guests on your sky tram system within two months to receive an additional $5,000 grant. Zoo attendance will decline a bit if you fail.</CHAlternateTransportShort>
      <CHAlternateTransportSuccessShort>You successfully transported 50 guests on your sky tram system. You have received a $5,000 grant.</CHAlternateTransportSuccessShort>
      <CHAlternateTransportSuccess>Good work! You have transported more than 50 guests on your sky tram within the alloted time and demonstrated that sky trams can be an effective method of transportation. The Alternate Transport Alliance has given you another $5,000 grant as a reward.</CHAlternateTransportSuccess>
      <CHAlternateTransportFailureShort>You were unable transport 50 guests on a sky tram within two months. Zoo attendance declined a bit due to the bad publicity.</CHAlternateTransportFailureShort>
      <CHAlternateTransportFailure>Two months have passed and you still have not transported 50 guests on your sky tram system. Since you have failed to meet the Alternate Transport Alliance's challenge you are not eligible for an additional grant, and the resulting bad publicity has caused zoo attendance to decline slightly for the next month.</CHAlternateTransportFailure>
      
      <CHZooFanQuarterly>The magazine Zoo Fan Quarterly is preparing an article about successful zoo tours called "Hit the Road" for a future issue. If you can raise $1,000 in donations from a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle tour within the next two months, Zoo Fan Quarterly will describe your accomplishment in their next issue. If you succeed, the good publicity will attract extra guests to your zoo and increase your zoo fame. If you fail, though, attendance at your zoo will decline slightly.
      <br/>
      Difficulty: Hard</CHZooFanQuarterly>
      <CHZooFanQuarterlyShort>Raise $1,000 in donations from a Jeep&#xAE; vehicle tour within two months.</CHZooFanQuarterlyShort>
      <CHZooFanQuarterlySuccessShort>Raising $1,000 in Jeep&#xAE; vehicle tour donations attracted extra guests to your zoo and made your zoo more famous.</CHZooFanQuarterlySuccessShort>
      <CHZooFanQuarterlySuccess>Well done! After you raised $1,000 in Jeep&#xAE; vehicle tour donations, Zoo Fan Quarterly published a glowing report on your zoo in their latest issue. The good publicity has attracted extra guests to your zoo and made your zoo more famous!</CHZooFanQuarterlySuccess>
      <CHZooFanQuarterlyFailureShort>You were unable to raise $1,000 in Jeep&#xAE; vehicle tour donations within two months. Zoo attendance has declined slightly as a result.</CHZooFanQuarterlyFailureShort>
      <CHZooFanQuarterlyFailure>Two months have passed and you still haven't raised $1,000 in Jeep&#xAE; vehicle tour donations. Zoo Fan Quarterly mentioned this disappointing news in their article about your zoo, and the bad publicity has caused zoo attendance to decline slightly. You will have fewer guests than normal for the next month.</CHZooFanQuarterlyFailure>
      
      <CHRainforestPreservation>The Rainforest Preservation Society promotes awareness of the world's threatened tropical rainforests and jungles. The society has made the following offer: if you construct six jungle-themed buildings in your zoo during the next two months, the society will give you a free animal--potentially even a tropical rainforest animal that you don't currently have. The buildings that count toward this challenge are: jungle-themed small and family restrooms, jungle-themed food and drink stands, and jungle-themed food carts.
      <br/>
      Difficulty: Easy</CHRainforestPreservation>
      <CHRainforestPreservationShort>Build six jungle-themed buildings within a two-month period. (Buildings that count towards this challenge: jungle-themed small and family restrooms, jungle-themed food and drink stands, and jungle-themed food carts.)</CHRainforestPreservationShort>
      <CHRainforestPreservationSuccessShort>You built six jungle-themed buildings, so the Rainforest Preservation Society awarded you a free animal.</CHRainforestPreservationSuccessShort>
      <CHRainforestPreservationSuccess>You've been busy! There are six new jungle-themed buildings in your zoo, which really impressed the Rainforest Preservation Society. The society has given you a %s in recognition of your efforts to promote rainforest awareness. You'll find the %s crated near the entrance to your zoo.</CHRainforestPreservationSuccess>
      <CHRainforestPreservationSuccessAlt>Congratulations! You've built six new jungle-themed buildings in your zoo, which has greatly impressed the Rainforest Preservation Society. The society couldn't find a tropical rainforest animal that you don't already have, so they have given you a %s instead. You'll find the %s crated near the entrance to your zoo.</CHRainforestPreservationSuccessAlt>      
      <CHRainforestPreservationFailureShort>You didn't build six jungle-themed buildings within the time limit, so the Rainforest Preservation Society didn't give you a free animal.</CHRainforestPreservationFailureShort>
      <CHRainforestPreservationFailure>Two months have passed and you still haven't built six jungle-themed buildings. The Rainforest Preservation Society's offer has expired, and you're no longer eligible to receive a free animal.</CHRainforestPreservationFailure>
      
   </Challengetext>
</ZT2Strings>
